For everyone trying to, like, stand on this internet and pontificate about, you know, Hamas, etc., etc., we need to just acknowledge one basic thing.
Israel is committing war crimes every single day.
Every single day they are committing war crimes.
This has been acknowledged. It has been identified.
And yet they are continued to do so indiscriminately.
This is no longer about opinion.
And this really is no longer about Hamas or the hostages.
Because at the end of the day, the efforts that they are taking in order to get Hamas or get the hostages are absolutely unconscionable and unhumanitarian.
So this whole thing of people going back and forth and arguing about, like, whether or not they care about, etc., stop.
The bottom line is that Israel is behaving in a barbaric fashion.
This has been identified unilaterally by humanitarian efforts, by the United Nations, etc.
And your defense of it means that you are not a humanitarian.
And we should stop trying to argue with you to try and prove that when the reality is it's in your face.
You don't f***ing care about humans that you've decided don't matter to you.
And you've decided they don't matter to you because you've listened to people tell you that they don't matter who actually you don't matter to.
I know. It's crazy.
I know.